[Music]
my name is diana alvargato
this is my manual life story i was a
typical new graduate when i started my
job as a software engineer in one of the
most prestigious research and
development company here in cebu city
like any single newbie who receives her
paycheck i often spend it on anything i
want and i often find myself short for
the next payday it was my mom who
insisted that i buy a manual life
insurance plan then i was lucky to meet
an agent who took his time explaining
the plan details well he was patient and
did not take offense when i asked
difficult questions five years later my
first child was born
nathan he was perfect yet he came with
multiple congenital defects i found out
that my manual life insurance plan
covers maternity benefit for my child
the fund we received helped us in the
medical expenses
unfortunately
my baby did not survive his surgery
before he turned a year old
we feel like our manulife policy
helped us overcome a very difficult time
in our lives
in 2017 i gave birth to my second child
haley and in 2020 i gave birth to
another daughter
and i'm happy to share that both of my
daughters are healthy and so full of
life
life insurance is something we thought
you will never need
but when you need it you hope you've had
it
[Music]
you